Why are you here? Why are you talking to me?
You've been sleeping, but you have to wake up now.
I can't. I don't know how.
Wake up. Someone you care about needs you.
You're here at last.
Sending you to rejoin your eyes within the acceptable limits of my interference.
But granting you this wish is all I can do.
After this, I cannot help.
I must get it back. At any cost.
I understand.
Go now.
Ah, yes. The dream must end.
How could I forget that was the last thing you said to me?
Cloud.
Hey, you're back!
Careful. You're going to trip and fall again.
Nah, I'm okay.
Kamui's already here. Why did he come home before the rest of you guys did?
Ah!
Mokuna was right. The feather's down here.
How do we get to the underground cavern where the water's kept?
You don't.
Huh?
Without special clearance, nobody's allowed underground.
But there's something important down there we have to find.
Water is the only thing underneath here.
No, it's not. There's a feather here, too.
You don't understand. We have to get down there.
You don't understand.
No, it will, foram.
I knew the villagers call the tower.
Let's go.
She isn't dead.
She's sleeping.
If she's just asleep, then why isn't she breathing?
It's not her body that's sleeping, it's her soul.
What is it?
The barrier that protects this building from the rain.
It's gone.
The power that's been locked in here, protecting this place for all these years, vanished.
It's been dormant for so long, but it seems to have pulled that girl inside.
Why doesn't she wake up?
It won't let her go.
She's trapped in sleep.
Where'd he go?
Only one person is supposed to be down there at a time.
As long as your friend makes no attempt to steal the water, Kamui won't kill him.
Is he okay?
Move out of my way.
His lips aren't moving, but I can still hear him.
I'll say it again.
Move.
The water pressure's too high.
I can barely move.
And I can't hold my breath much longer.
I can't hold my breath much longer.
So, you are game.
That's the same thing he said the first time we met.
I can't hold my breath much longer.
You don't know.
I can read my mind.
It means food.
Then I can't hold my breath much longer.
The water pressure's too high.
I can barely move.
And I can't hold my breath much longer.
So, you are game.
That's the same thing he said the first time we met.
What does he mean?
You don't know.
He can read my mind.
it means food what wait I know that move
if he drinks all your blood that may be enough to wake him from this sleep subaru
the vampire twins it's them
I knew I recognized that move you know him don't you he taught you how to fight
I don't sense his presence here in Tokyo but it appears he sent his little protégé
which means he might not be far behind subaru please wake up if we don't hurry
he's going to catch us if that happens I will kill him but for now
it's your turn
please don't do it
please wake up
stay back you won't get the feather I must retrieve them all at any cost
you won't
you can't
wake up
or you'll lose the person you care about more than anyone else
I would never expect game to have so much power game is created so their blood can become
our food they're nothing but soul as imitations of human beings
are you his master
no
then I was right he belongs to that hunter
the same man who subaru gave his blood to
no I know him he's a good person all he wants is to protect sakura and help her find the memory feathers
and the memory feathers
the seal on Shaaron's right eye
has broken
that clone is my creation a duplicate of clow reed's last descendant created to gather the feathers
his life has no other purpose
he'll fight to return the feathers to the princess of clow country
eliminating anyone who stands in his way
that's all he knows that's how he was made however
the true shower on placed a piece of his own soul in the clones right eye
complicating my plan
once the true shower on was restrained and safely imprisoned again
I tried to remove the tainted eye from my duplicate
but clow reed's descendant had planned well
if I took out the eye he had planted the clone would also be destroyed
unfortunately it is impossible to make multiple duplicates of the same person
besides I cared little if my creation had another's soul
all that mattered to me was that I had made someone whose single goal would be to collect those feathers
so I used him in that altered state
I discovered the right time in the right place
and sent the duplicate to clow country
where he would befriend the princess who was the key to the power of the ruins
and so as I watched and waited
my plan was set in motion
everything was moving along exactly as I had wanted
right up until that witch began meddling
when shower on gave away his eye he lost half of his magical power with it
weakened by that loss he was unable to break free from his prison
time passed and he grew
always watching always waiting
paying the price with each year of his imprisonment
Fei Wang's magic is powerful
like shower on he too is a descendant of clow reed born with the incredible power of that line
additionally he is motivated by the single-minded purpose of granting his own wish
there are limits to how much I can interfere I could not directly oppose his plan
for that same reason I was unable to help shower on break free from his captivity
so I too have been waiting for the true shower on to wake up
when he awoke the seal that bound the duplicates left eye imbuing it with a piece of shower on soul broke open
it could not hold any longer because that piece of soul had to be reunited with its rightful owner
will shower on make it there in time
you were the one who helped shower on cross dimensions and reach the witch weren't you
knowing your origin my failed creation I should have anticipated this inevitable outcome
so Xinhua did you sympathize with him
what you have no answer
did you know you've been traveling with something that isn't human
you're suppressing it now but I can tell you possess great magic
you must have known that is you call it a soul right
that is soul actually belong to someone else
couldn't you tell
the power in his eye is fading
someone's coming from another dimension not the man who was hunting us
the other shower is coming
the magic is almost gone
that soul belongs to you
it was created by your love for Sakura and everyone else in your life
it's a part of you
and I'm not going to let you lose it
at first the power I sensed came from bat but now it's coming from the portal
now it's coming from the portal
you shall run
don't
was that the only feather that was in this world?
you can use magic right?
that eye is the source of your power
You can use magic, right?
That eye is the source of your power.
In order to collect all the feathers, I'm going to have to take that from you.
The barrier that protected City Hall has fallen.
Something must be wrong in the underground cistern.
You can't take a weapon in there without special clearance.
What happened?
We must be drawing near to the place where her soul is sleeping.
Most likely her body went to join it.
Killer Poop! Shaolin and Mai won't come out of the water!
What?
This eye... has changed.
What are you doing?
You ain't a sigh.
What's happened to you?
I'll take the other as well.
Let him go. Give them to me.
His blue eyes are the source of his power.
Once I have those, I'll have no need for him anymore.
Let him go!
Stop it!
Does he know his arm's broken?
He doesn't care. It's like he can't feel pain in his body.
Or in his heart, either.
Charon!
Kurupu!
Fi!
You aren't him.
You're not the kid, are you?
You look the same.
But your presence feels different.
I will collect the feathers.
At any cost.
That felt like fire's magic!
Maybe that means he's still okay!
You ate his hide to steal his magic?
I'll take anything I need if it's going to help me collect the feathers and kill who I must.
He gave up everything for you and Princess Sakura. Did you know that?
He would have died for you and this is how you choose to repay him?
Can you hear me, kid? Can you?
No!
Somebody I care about.
The person I care about more than anybody else in my life.
Oh no!
Charon!
half of my soul i gave you this a long time ago once i awoke and the seal was broken the magician
did everything in his power to make sure it stayed with you and for that he lost one of his eyes
but it doesn't matter how hard you try once broken a seal cannot be repaired
i'm sure the magician knew that but he tried anyway for your sake
it seems he didn't make it after all
can you hear me everyone shihara please hear me i've always been with you watching through your
right eye this whole time everything you've been through in your life everyone you've met
it wasn't my soul that loved princess sakura that part of it was all yours wasn't it
i'm gonna fight him i need my sword
come on furball give it to me
okay
no ron no
what are you doing what's going on
when i gave up half my soul to you i looked in through your eye and said that it wouldn't
always be necessary i told you that if enough time passed before the seal on your right eye
was broken you would change for good you would form a soul of your own and you wouldn't need
mine anymore i thought for sure that everything you did and everyone you met would help you create a soul
that was yours alone
but i also promised you that when the time came for the seal to break open
if you had not yet discovered a soul within yourself
if you were still motivated only by the orders your master gave you when he made you
i would destroy you
Shaoran, no!
Please, just don't kill him!
Shaoran, please!
Come, wait!
Subar, please!
No!
Wait!
Please, don't!
Shaoran, what?
I will collect the feathers, at any cost.
There are no more feathers to collect in this world,
so I see no reason for me to stay here any longer.
I'm ready to move on to the next world.
Please, don't leave me!
Shaoran...
Shara
I'm sorry.
You woke up at the most painful moment possible, didn't you?
Subaru!
At last, you're finally awake.
I'm sorry you've been alone all this time.
Quickly, we must move on to a new world.
Not yet.
But we have to go before the hunter catches up to us.
Please, brother. Wait.
You tell me, what is that crest you're wearing?
You already know. It's the crest of the man who killed your mother.
It's the crest of the man who killed your mother.
Thank you.
Okay.
知りたい愛するってどんなこと君が微笑むと世界は少し震って輝いたまるで呼吸するように動き出した
ねえ僕は僕は知りたい生きてくってどんなこと僕が重ねると世界は少し震って輝いた
僕に眠る真実を今静かに解き放つ
知りたい生きてくってどんなこと君が重ねると世界は少し震って輝いたまるで呼吸するように動き出した